(Living as Myself)
It's time to bring in the star of the Rainbow Live.
When the preview aired, we received many comments like...
- "She'll really be on the show?" - Right.
She's a member of a nationally beloved girl group.
- Right. - Yes.
It's Girls' Generation now. Here's Yu Ri.
(It's Girls' Generation now. Here's Yu Ri.)
- Hello. - Hello.
(The idol of idol groups who made history in the K-pop scene)
(The star of cheerful and wholesome charms)
(The member of a legendary girl group, Girls' Generation)
(Singer and Actress Yu Ri)
Welcome to the Rainbow Club.
Please say hello to our viewers.
Hello. I'm a member of Girls' Generation, Yu Ri.
I'm also an actress. My full name is Kwon Yu Ri.
Nice to meet you all.
I was very surprised because I just assumed that...
she had been on the show.
- Really? - Yes.
I'm the first member of my group to share my day-to-day life...
- on a TV show. - You're the first one?
- Yes. I'm the first one. - She is.
Actually, it's my first time sharing my day-to-day life at all.
- Right. - It's my very first time.
Anyway...
- I'm nervous. - Wait.
Sung Hwan is more nervous than you.
Why does he keep getting nervous these days?
- Why are you so nervous? - He's nervous all the time.
- Okay. - Do you have hand tremors?
- Why... - You're such a goofball.
It must be your blood sugar.
Here's the thing. Back in my day,
- Back in your day? - Girls' Generation...
- Many years ago when I was younger, - Right.
Girls' Generation...
- Right. - was a sensation.
- They're still the best. - They are the best.
Yes.
(The Kumquat-Tinted World)
"The Kumquat-Tinted World."
(Sleeping)
- Gosh. - Oh, no.
(Only her foot is sticking out.)
(Yu Ri is sleeping, buried under the blanket.)
(Wriggling)
(Sighing)
(Groaning)
(Getting up)
All right.
- All right. - She's groaning.
Isn't this embarrassing?
(Nodding)
I love that she's making the bed right away.
(She quickly makes the bed.)
(That's great.)
(Opening)
- It's a simple house. - Yes. It looks clean.
Right. It looks very clean.
(Turning on the lamp)
Is it a low-rise apartment?
Isn't it a high-rise apartment?
(Grunting)
(Stretching)
My gosh.
- She's groaning a lot this morning. - She's...
Hello.
I've been living alone for three years.
I'm a member of Girls' Generation and an actress, Kwon Yu Ri.
(Singer and Actress Yu Ri)
I live on the east side of Jeju Island.
You live on Jeju Island.
It's one of my fantasies.
(It's not frequented by tourists.)
Why did you decide to live in the eastern part?
I felt this bright energy from the eastern part.
Gosh, how nice.
- It's a single-family house. - It's a single-family house.
In Jeju, we call it living on a yearly lease.
- Right. - We don't put down a big deposit.
We rent houses...
on a yearly basis to live here.
I also rented this house on a yearly basis.
(Walking into her house...)
It looks neat.
How relaxing. It's nice and clean.
Jeju Island was the first place I ever lived alone.
I could decorate the house to my own taste...
and do things just the way I wanted.
- I was free to do that. - Right.
Right. It's nice and simple.
(Her own paintings are hanging all over the house.)
(Exuding the Jeju vibe...)
- This shows her personality. - Right.
(are the cute decor items.)
This house has almost everything I like.
How did you end up moving there?
- First of all, I love yoga. - Okay.
- I also love nature. - Okay.
In Seoul, I've always been...
- so busy with work. - Right.
I sought out a slower pace of life.
- That's why. - I think I can guess it.
- I can guess the yearly rent. - Okay.
- How? - How much?
I bet it's around 10,000 dollars. Or is it 9,000 dollars?
- You're in the ballpark. - I am, right?
- You're so close. - Have you looked into houses?
- Yes. Jeju Island... - Right. It's Jeju Island.
My mother used to have yearly leases too.
- Yes. It's under 9,000 dollars. - He was spot on.
- It's lower than that? - Yes, much lower.
- It's much lower than that. - It's very cheap.
- You found a good home then. - That's a really good deal then.
(She goes to the bathroom as soon as she wakes up.)
(She brushes her teeth right away.)
(Tying her hair)
(She thoroughly washes her face.)
(Refreshed)
Nice.
(Walking over)
(It's located right in front of the bathroom.)
My dressing table.
You don't have a lot of cosmetics.
- I rarely need to wear makeup. - Right.
Okay.
(Pumping)
All right.
(Spreading it without hesitation)
(Applying the leftover on her body)
Sunscreen.
You always wear sunscreen.
I sometimes apply sunscreen instead of lotion.
(I sometimes apply sunscreen instead of lotion.)
(She roughly applies it on her face.)
All done.
(Wiping the residue on her body)
(She's done with her all-in-one skincare routine.)
- That's it for your face? - Yes.
She doesn't even put on essence.
It takes about the same amount of time as my skincare routine.
I bet.
Okay.
Gosh, it's so humid.
(Opening)
But the air must feel so fresh.
She breathes in fresh air every morning.
- She lives on Jeju Island. - Right.
(Lifting something)
- A dehumidifier? - Is it a dehumidifier?
- It's that humid? - That's how much moisture...
it collects in a day.
The alarm wakes me up.
- It means the dehumidifier is full. - Really?
- I wake up at the alarm. - That's a lot of water.
I have to keep the dehumidifier on all the time.
I live right by the beach.
So it's super humid.
Jeju Island is definitely more humid.
- That's why she's studying houses. - That's why.
- The wallpaper is coming loose. - You can't do anything about it.
Right. There's a leak. My mom's place has a leak too.
- Well, it's an island, after all. - Right.
- Right. - Moisture absorbers.
- Moisture absorbers. - I can't live without them.
Here's my routine. When I wake up,
I empty out the dehumidifier which is filled to the brim.
I empty it out three times a day in summer.
(After emptying out the water from the dehumidifier, )
(she turns it back on immediately.)
(She lights a scented candle after turning on a dehumidifier.)
(She's lighting more than one?)
These scented candles help reduce humidity in my house.
Lighting scented candles became part of my routine.
- Yes. People should light them. - Right.
(Humming)
(Shaking her legs)
She's excited.
She easily gets excited.
(Shaking her legs)
(After lighting the scented candles, she keeps on humming.)
(She grabs a vacuum cleaner and goes to the living room.)
My gosh.
(She plugs in the power cord.)
(Tossing the cord over her shoulder)
She threw the power cord over her shoulder.
A lot of people have switched over...
- to cordless vacuum cleaners. - Right.
But I bought most of my household items...
from a secondhand marketplace.
- The table. - Really?
And the sofa too. It was only 30 dollars.
- I bought my fridge on the app. - Right.
- You bought everything used. - Actually, I found the listing...
- on the app too. - What?
- The house too? - That's common on the island.
- You found your house on the app? - Yes.
- I guess so. It's robust. - This app has a robust community.
- Yu Ri is so frugal. - Totally.
(She cleans every nook and corner with a used vacuum cleaner.)
I need to give more attention to these corners.
(Suddenly turning off the vacuum cleaner)
What's going on?
What do I do with this spider?
- My gosh. - Oh, no.
Jeju Island is great, but there are a lot of bugs.
You have to compromise on certain things...
- when you live there. - Right.
I have to live with bugs. But they scare me every time.
(She grabs a paper cup from the cabinet.)
Hey, spider.
(Catching it on her first try)
There it is.
I should release it.
She's going to spare it.
- She caught it alive. - She should spare it.
(Sliding)
(Safely delivering it back to nature)
Have a good life.
Great job. She spared it.
(Let me see.)
(Grabbing a plastic bag)
(Frowning)
- What is it? - I bet there are bugs.
- She must've seen something. - There must be bugs in there.
(Scratching)
Come on.
- Gosh, why so many legs? - What's that?
- It looks like a camel cricket. - It's a camel cricket.
(Screaming)
(I can do this.)
(But she's struggling to catch it as it's the biggest one yet.)
- The body is split in half. - My goodness!
- I hate bugs. - It's not a cockroach, right?
I don't think it is.
(She barely manages to take care of it.)
Come on.
Goodbye.
- "Goodbye." - "Goodbye."
- She has a kind heart. - I got it.
(This is it for me.)
Seriously. This is killing me.
(Exhausted)
(Her cleaning session comes to an abrupt end.)
Okay.
(Yu Ri comes into the kitchen after getting changed.)
Good job.
I started to talk to myself a lot...
- when I began living alone. - Of course.
- I didn't get why people did that. - Right.
- It's... - But I became one of them.
I need to eat something.
(Talking to herself again)
What will she eat?
Let me take out the yam.
She's taking what out?
(The yam is frozen.)
Yam?
- You froze the yam? - Yes. I like yam.
(She grabs milk and an apple too.)
(Rustling)
(Transferring the frozen yam pieces first)
(Too big to go in)
(Let me see.)
- She's so down-to-earth. - Yu Ri is just like us.
- That's the most effective way. - She's just like us.
She's just like one of us. Right.
Okay.
(The yam is broken into small pieces.)
(Feeling proud)
(Adding apple pieces as well)
I've been following this routine for 20 years now.
- Really? - Yes.
- Apples. - You've had yams for 20 years?
(She adds milk...)
(and honey too.)
My mother used to make this for me since high school.
- Oh, this? - Yes. A lot of moms used to...
- make this shake. - I had to drink it for breakfast.
Right. My mom used to make this too.
(She's been blending it for 20 years.)
This yam juice helped me boost my energy.
- It's good for immune system too. - I should try that.
The weather...
Let me check the weather.
(Looking up the weather on Jeju Island)
Gosh, what a relief.
It won't rain today.
Okay. Nice.
No rain forecast on AccuWeather.
No rain forecast on the Weather Channel.
No rain forecast on the news either.
It won't rain. It'll just be cloudy.
Does it rain often on the island?
The weather affects me a lot.
- I do a lot of outdoor activities. - I see.
You're like a haenyeo. You're checking the weather.
- Right. - Well, that's my dream.
(Yu Ri checks the weather like a haenyeo.)
Okay.
(Meanwhile, her breakfast is ready.)
Okay. I don't think I can make it by 7pm.
(The yam juice she's been drinking for 20 years)
(Humming in approval)
Her diet reminds me of my grandmother.
- Right. - Her diet is very healthy.
My grandmother was 110 years old when she passed.
Your routine is very similar to my grandmother's.
Let me get ready to go out. All done. Okay.
I should get changed now.
(She quickly changes her outfit to go out.)
She's going out.
(She casually picks up her bag.)
You know, there's a popular fashion style on the island.
- Right. - That looks like the local style.
- The cool-islander outfit. - That's right.
The stylish girl on the island.
That's the kind of outfit my mom wears.
- Look at her. - That's right.
Recently, there was a bazaar on the island to help...
- abandoned dogs. - Yes.
I was part of the bazaar too.
- Really? - I saw your mother...
- at the event. - Right.
- She told me. - Really?
She's very famous on the island.
- Everyone knows... - The president.
- The dog president? - that her dog is the president.
My mom wants him to get reelected, but I don't know.
- Wasn't it Alkong? - Already?
No, Dalkong.
That small dog has power.
I'd love to see him again.
Wait. A helmet?
- A helmet. - What?
(She goes somewhere while holding a helmet.)
- It's a scooter. - I love it.
That's all you need on Jeju Island.
This is my favorite mode of transportation on the island.
It's the scooter.
I have the Class Two Small Motorcycle License.
- On your 1st try? - I passed the test on my 1st try.
- You got the license. - Yes.
Didn't Sung Hwan take the test 3 or 4 times?
- Gosh, here it is. - Wait.
- Right. - There it is.
You lose points if you put your feet down.
- That was so bad. - Gosh.
I must go out on a great day like this.
I drive a small scooter on the island...
as well as a big liter-class motorcycle.
- You do? - Yes.
We should go for a ride together.
- Totally. - I mean it.
- It's going to be so great. - That sounds fun.
Let's go to Jeju Island.
I can lift my front wheel.
(Trembling in fear)
(She puts on the helmet like a pro.)
(Turning on the engine at once)
(Vroom)
(Let's head out.)
(You can't be on the road without music.)
- The weather is amazing. - Gosh, a ride by the ocean.
- Gosh, that's so cool. - That's part of my daily life.
- I do that every day. - There's no one around.
That's close from my home. I do that often.
- That's close from your home? - Yes.
- It's close from my home. - You picked the perfect song.
You know it, right?
I'm already getting excited.
You have to sing along.
It's an immortal song.
I love it.
- It's a scene in a fairytale. - I feel peaceful just watching it.
You can't feel the same vibe when you ride your bike in Seoul.
- I mean, look at her smile. - Exactly.
That's from genuine joy.
Oh, my. It's summer!
(She happily sings several songs with her nasal voice.)
(Yu Ri arrives at a place.)
Ddonggeul!
- It's a dog. - Oh, my.
- Gosh, so cute. - Goodness.
- It's a brindle dog. - Ddonggeul.
- Ddonggeul. - How cute.
Ddonggeul.
(Did you miss me, Ddonggeul?)
- Can Ddonggeul stand on two feet? - Ddonggeul is so happy to see you.
- Right. - Is it a Jindo dog?
She's a Hogu which is a tiger-striped Jindo.
She's a puppy at a fish farm. Her name is Ddonggeul.
- Goodness. She likes that. - Gosh, she's showing her belly.
- I... - She's still a baby.
- My goodness. - She's only two.
- That's a baby. - So she's only two.
- Two years... - Jindo dogs show their belly...
only to their owners.
- Right. - Yes.
I met her two years ago when she was a tiny puppy.
- You met when she was a baby. - Yes.
- I was riding my scooter. - How beautiful.
- I spotted her and became friends. - She grew so big, so fast.
Ddonggeul is only two years old.
- She's so energetic... - She must be full of energy.
- and lively. - She's full of youth.
- The owner and workers... - Look at her.
Work during the day.
But I'm a freelancer.
I sometimes go and walk her. I play with her too.
- You play with her. - That's it.
- How beautiful. - You're so sweet.
I'll give you a treat. How about a treat?
(Following her)
- How cute. - How about a treat?
Hello, sir.
Sir, I'm here!
- Sit, Ddonggeul. - Hey.
Ddonggeul, sit. She's good at that, right?
- Down. - Sit.
What a cute dog.
- Down. - Down.
What a cutie. Well done.
- She's so friendly. - Sir.
I guess she knows it's me.
- Of course. - That's why she's so happy.
- Of course. - You come every day.
- She waits for you. - Right?
- It's fascinating. - My gosh.
- She can tell... - She knows everything.
I'm coming by the engine sound.
- She knows it's me. - Yes.
- That's right. - Yes.
She can tell it's you even from a distance.
Ddonggeul. You're so cute.
Get some water. And we'll go.
Let's go for a walk.
- Let's go. - I see. You...
- Yes. I walk her. - You walk her?
- Gosh, the owner must be so happy. - Let's go for a walk.
That's why he sometimes gives me octopus.
- He wants to thank me. - Do you walk her often?
Yes, I walk her when I'm there. At least once a day.
At least once a day?
Are you working as a dogwalker as a side hustle?
No.
I think it might be your part-time job.
- I just like doing that. - You just like that?
- I like the neighborhood dogs. - Right. That's...
And they like me too.
Let's go.
Let's go!
Ddonggeul is super friendly.
- She's a sweet one. - Ddonggeul.
Great job.
Ddonggeul, you're a pro at this.
Ddonggeul.
Ddonggeul. How is it possible...
that you can walk so calmly like this?
I can tell she does this often.
- They both know each other's pace. - Right.
- They know each other's gait. - Yes, they do.
(Grinning)
(Patting)
It's hot, right? Let's hurry.
Let's walk fast. Go.
One, two.
- That's a real run. - Ddonggeul must be so happy.
Exactly. She must be a happy dog.
- Ddonggeul is matching my pace. - Let's go.
Ddonggeul, thank you...
for matching my pace.
We're back. Yes?
- Did she have fun? - Yes, totally.
She can't stop looking at you.
- Sir, I'll be back tomorrow. - Yes? Sure.
Walk her again tomorrow.
(Wagging her tail)
Look at her wagging her tail. Oh, my.
I bet Ddonggeul always waits for this time of the day.
Bye. See you. The walk is over.
I'm off. See you around.
- Bye. - Bye.
(She goes to the next spot after saying goodbye to Ddonggeul.)
- I'm off, sir. - See you.
Bye.
Oh, the smell of the sea urchins.
I can smell the sea urchins.
- Sea urchins. - It's the sea urchin season.
I'd love to have sea urchin noodles.
(While breathing in the smell of the Jeju ocean, )
(she eagerly rides her scooter and arrives at some place.)
(I'm here!)
(Striding in)
- Hello. - Welcome.
- You're here. - I'm here.
- Hello. - You're here.
- Ma'am. - She went to the restroom.
This is my go-to restaurant on the island.
I became close to the owners of the restaurant after moving here.
And just like me, they have an acting career.
We have a lot of similar interests.
When I first decided to settle down here,
they helped me a lot, so my relocation process...
would go smoothly. They helped me become independent.
I'm here.
Gosh, the kids are here.
- Hey. - Hello.
- Hello, Seung Woo. - Hello.
- Hello. - Hi.
- You're friends with everyone. - Hi.
We're all neighbors.
- Chief Kwon. - The neighborhood.
- Right. That's my nickname. - It's like "Hometown Cha-Cha-Cha."
- She's the neighborhood chief. - "Hometown Cha-Cha-Cha."
- I... - What do you want to eat?
- I'm so hungry. - What did you do today?
I'm so hungry.
(What should I eat?)
Did you guys eat? Did your husband and mom eat?
- We haven't eaten yet. - Let's eat together then.
Okay. I want the octopus ramyeon.
- Ramyeon? - I haven't had it in a while.
I must have some ramyeon.
Okay.
(She places her order like a regular.)
(She grabs the side dishes like it's nothing new.)
- You guys are real friends. - Yes, we're close.
- Right. - She serves her own food.
- Yes. - This is nice.
(Comfortable)
This is nice.
I'm hungry. Let's eat together.
There will be too much food for me.
(Octopus ramyeon arrives!)
Here it is.
(Excited)
(It's full of seafood from the Jeju Island's sea.)
It looks so delicious.
- This is insane. - Seriously.
It's a whole octopus.
- Clams. - Octopus ramyeon.
(It makes her mouth water.)
I haven't had ramyeon with white soup in a while.
I'm so hungry.
- It looks so tasty. - Enjoy it.
(A heap of food)
Go ahead and eat.
Thank you for the food. You gave me a big abalone.
- Go ahead and eat. - It looks delicious.
- This is insane. - Thank you for the food.
(Gulping)
(Trying a spoonful of soup)
(Impressed)
This is the taste I like.
They're eating together.
- Yes. - They're like a family.
Thankfully, it was between lunch and dinner.
- Ramyeon is best for that time. - It was...
time for them to eat.
(She begins inhaling the noodles in earnest.)
(Slurping)
She eats with gusto.
Yu Ri eats a big amount of food.
- That's right. - Yes. She is like that.
(Let's see.)
Don't we need more?
- We need more, right? - I think we do.
- Honestly, this isn't enough. - Honestly, this isn't enough.
I agree.
- Go ahead. - Should we mix it with rice...
- in here? - No.
(The second dish, stir-fried octopus gets served.)
Look at the seasoning.
- They're good. - That's the real deal.
- They're good. - The seasoning is dark in color.
- Really? - I'll do it.
- I'll do it well. - Here we go.
This stir-fried dish has a smoky flavor.
It has a smoky flavor.
- It looks like it does. - This is driving me crazy.
- It smells good. - High heat makes it tasty.
Exactly.
Mom said she'd give me her recipe.
Knowing her for three years won't be enough.
It won't be enough.
You'll need to work as a server.
- Work as a server? - That's right.
I want to know her recipe for the broth...
- and sauce. - It has a smoky flavor.
- But she won't teach you. - No.
Even if you cook with the same ingredients in Seoul,
- it won't taste the same. - The ingredients will be different.
The ingredients are so fresh there.
I think I have a clue.
(Let's forget about the recipe and mix the dish with rice.)
I don't want to watch this.
- For what? - For a smoky flavor.
(Opening her mouth wide)
(The taste makes her clap.)
The combination of these two dishes is insane.
- I know. - Right?
I see why you live on Jeju Island.
You want to eat tasty food.
You should set up some laver flakes, right?
- You said what I wanted to say. - Seriously.
- We're practically eating together. - That's right.
Yes.
I'm setting up some laver flakes.
I'm sprinkling some pepper.
They're like two large babies.
(They're like two large babies.)
I'm eating it with dried laver in my imagination.
I'm getting a spoonful.
(It's as tasty as I expected.)
It's as I expected.
You need to eat some rice.
(Scraping the bottom of the bowl)
It was a nice meal.
(As if she is used to it, she cleans up after herself.)
(Lifting)
- They're like a family. - I know. They're her family.
It'll feel incredible to nap there.
- I've napped there. - Nice.
- You should lie down right away. - When there are no customers...
- on a rainy day... - She is like a part-timer there.
This kimchi tastes incredible with ramyeon.
(Slapping)
I'm so happy to hear that.
- It smells incredible, right? - It's nice.
Eat young radish kimchi with spicy noodles.
- It'll be good with noodles. - Young radish kimchi naengmyeon.
- There is a thin film of ice. - Yes.
Being on Jeju Island isn't the only good thing.
- Being surrounded by people... - Those people are so nice. I know.
Here they are
I'll enjoy them
I'll think of you every time I eat.
Here.
(She pays for her meal.)
She pays right away.
Soo Hyun, why...
What? Didn't it go through?
- It's just for octopus ramyeon. - Did she charge 1,000 dollars?
- Did you get ripped off? - Don't be ridiculous.
I bet she paid 460 dollars.
We're close. For goodness' sake.
It's just for octopus ramyeon. I ate stir-fried octopus too.
(I ate stir-fried octopus too. Why is the bill so small?)
- It's fine. - Seriously.
Seriously.
- Gosh, she is cool. - She is cool.
Soo Hyun is totally cool. She has a girl-crush vibe.
You're so funny.
- See you tomorrow. - That kind of love is rare now.
Hyun Bin, I'm leaving. Mom, thank you for the food.
- Okay. Bye. - Bye.
- Bye. - Take care.
- I'm leaving. Don't come outside. - Okay.
- Drive safely. - Okay, I will.
At all times.
At all times,
I'll drive safely.
- Watch out for the cars. - Okay.
- She is like an older sister. - I know. She is my older sister.
(I'm leaving.)
(Driving)
What time is it now? It's 5pm.
The tide is low at 6pm.
It'll be at its lowest.
- Where is she going? - I'll be able to find it, right?
- Will you harvest something? - Yes.
- I check the tide often. - Is she really a haenyeo?
- What? - There must be something.
Seriously. No way.
- Will she go into the water? - I think she will.
- There are skin divers... - She'll go into the water.
Behind her.
I'm here!
Let's see.
(Taking out)
(She arrives at the beach with a mesh bag.)
(Oh, my!)
(The blue Jeju Island's sea)
That's my mart.
- Your mart. - It's so nice. It's your mart.
Yes.
(Rolling up)
(She ties her hair haphazardly.)
(She puts on gloves.)
Here is hijiki.
- Hijiki? Will you harvest hijiki? - I think...
- Hijiki. - Hijiki?
These days...
I went to the Sumapo Coast to harvest some plump hijiki.
I heard that there was a lot of hijiki,
so I went there to harvest it.
It's hijiki.
- It had hijiki on its head. - I see.
There are a lot of sea snails and hijiki these days.
You can also find blue crabs.
- Blue crabs? - Yes. Blue crabs are in season...
- these days. - Blue crabs.
They're blue-colored crabs.
It really is a mart. It has all the seasonal ingredients.
- It's a mart. - It really is...
a mart that gives freely.
- I see. - You get food from nature.
- Can you take it as you want? - No.
You can only harvest it in designated areas.
- I see. - The permitted areas.
You can only harvest it in permitted areas.
So you can't take it as you want.
- No, you can't. - You'll get arrested.
This is incredible.
- Anyone can do it. - You can harvest it like that.
It's hijiki.
(There is hijiki everywhere.)
There is so much.
(She turns greedy.)
It's like a gold mine!
(They don't pay her any mind.)
(This mart has good hijiki.)
Isn't Yu Ri a natural person?
- She is so easygoing. - Still,
it suits her. She has a cool life.
This is enough.
This is more than enough.
If I want more, I can always come back.
I got too much.
- She got a lot. - It's a lot.
Let's go.
I need to go now.
Is it 6:30pm? I need to hurry up.
(Hurrying)
Where is Chief Kwon going now?
- Chief Kwon is busy. - Chief Kwon.
- She is so busy. - On Jeju Island,
- I'm so busy. - Good.
(She hangs the harvested hijiki at the front.)
(Chief Kwon sets off again.)
- The sun is setting. - How cool.
The sun sets so quickly.
- It really does. - You're right.
All right.
She came home after visiting a mart.
(Chief Kwon returns home after grocery shopping.)
(Taking out)
Here.
That's good.
(She puts the mesh bag with hijiki in the sink.)
(I don't have much time.)
What time is it now?
What does she want to watch?
- What? - Baseball?
(Baseball?)
- Which team are you a fan of? - You're a baseball fan.
(It's nice to meet you.)
I'm a fan of Hanwha Eagles.
- Eagles? - Hanwha Eagles?
That's right.
My team will catch up with yours soon.
- They have a long way to go. - It'll happen soon.
- Right now... - They need to be diligent.
- Your team is ranked higher. - Of course.
- They placed second. - Yes.
Gosh.
(Without putting down her backpack, )
(she becomes absorbed in Hanwha Eagles' game.)
Si Hwan.
(My team is losing.)
Okay. Now, it's...
the fourth inning.
It's okay.
Now...
Okay. Since we're losing,
I'll soak the hijiki.
Firstly,
the hijiki.
(Water running)
She is cooking. She needs to eat dinner.
The amount you'll eat.
Cook only the amount you'll eat.
(She rinses the amount she'll eat and puts it in a container.)
What will she make with hijiki?
If you order jjajangmyeon...
and put hijiki on the top,
- it's really tasty. - Really?
Do you need to order jjajangmyeon to eat hijiki in a tasty way?
She'll use any excuse to eat more food.
(In this case, jjajangmyeon is her goal.)
(Glancing over)
(Glancing over again while getting water)
She watches the game.
- She is different from Shin Young. - Her gaze... No.
I've never seen you watch the game like that.
- I watch the game too. - She is definitely different.
I watch the game like this.
Have you no conscience? You don't even make a side glance.
You look at the glass noodles.
(The baseball game was playing right before her eyes.)
(But her eyes were fixed on the glass noodles.)
Do you only watch the highlights?
- No! - "No!"
She watched a lot of highlight videos.
(I bet she watched a lot of highlight videos.)
If you attack my love for baseball, I won't leave you be.
I'll pull out all of your hair!
- I don't mind anything else. - I mean...
You can criticize my family, but not my love for baseball!
- Okay? - Let's talk when your team wins.
- For goodness' sake! - Let's talk when your team wins.
Since when were you so critical?
(She continues to cook as she wishes for her team's victory.)
(Taking out)
It's pollack roe.
My dinner menu is...
pollack roe and hijiki pot rice.
- Pot rice. - It's the dish I enjoy the most.
- It's so tasty. - It's bound to be delicious.
Let's add vinegar.
It removes the fishy taste.
It removes the smell of the sea.
(She adds the soaked hijiki.)
- Hijiki. - It'll become soft.
(The color changes as soon as it's in the water.)
- Ten seconds are enough... - Don't leave it in for long.
For blanching.
- Take it out as soon as it's green. - You're right.
(She takes out the cooked hijiki in a pretty shade of green.)
(Picking up)
- That's a proper pot. - It's a pot.
(She makes a simple broth with a broth tablet.)
That's right. Broth tablets are the best.
Adding the broth...
- deepens the flavors. - You're right.
You cook so easily.
You add so much hijiki compared to the amount of rice.
I like hijiki.
That's the charm of cooking at home.
You can add as much as you want.
(Grabbing)
(Ripping)
(Pushing out)
It looks tasty.
- That's it. Butter. - Butter.
That's right. Put it in there.
Nice.
How will she cook it?
- I don't want it to splatter. - The inside...
bursts because it's roe.
She pan-fries it.
(The pollack roe cooks cleanly in parchment paper.)
- It's a fascinating method. - I know.
The rice is ready.
Let's go.
(The rice is ready.)
The intersection of time and love...
(Let's hurry up and eat.)
All right.
(She opens the lid.)
My goodness. There are hijiki and scallions.
I eat hearty meals.
It looks tasty.
Sesame oil.
(She adds sesame oil for nuttiness.)
This is great. My goodness.
It looks incredible.
Gosh, there is scorched rice.
Look at that scorched rice.
It looks amazing.
Scorched rice.
(Hijiki she harvested and pollack roe stir-fried in butter)
There is so much hijiki.
She eats it with soy sauce.
- It looks tasty. - She knows how to eat.
- If you sprinkle some pepper... - That's right.
- Exactly. - Sung Hwan.
- I had the same thought. - Me too.
A bit of pepper will be nice.
(She takes a big spoonful.)
It looks so tasty.
She took a big mouthful.
(It's amazing.)
(This is it.)
The one you get at a restaurant doesn't have that much hijiki.
- It only has a tiny bit. - Yes. Same with thistle rice.
It's so tasty.
(She takes another mouthful.)
(Her mouth moves busily.)
- She eats with so much gusto. - It looks delicious.
My goodness. She eats with gusto.
It looks tasty.
(But her eyes are fixed on TV.)
A grounder. It's a strikeout.
They'll need to do that.
(Grabbing)
Makgeolli.
Nice.
(Shall I have a drink?)
(Drinking)
It's nice.
(Leaning)
(The sky turns dark.)
When I worked very busily,
the fancy spotlights...
and the endless schedule...
brought me happiness...
and popularity.
But I felt a sense of emptiness...
as an individual.
"What are the things..."
"I can do by myself?"
When I thought about the answer, the list was very short.
But on Jeju Island,
I gained a lot of courage.
I don't know why living here gives me...
so much courage.
On Jeju Island, you focus more on eating and living.
That's right.
Instead of worrying about how you look...
and what people will think,
you live very close to nature.
Looking at the sea takes a load off your chest.
"Kwon Yu Ri, you can do it!"
"Give it a go! Face it head-on!"
Vroom!
(Then you set off.)
Then you set off. Vroom!
(Vroom)
(Embarrassed)
(She drove around the neighborhood...)
(and gained strength throughout the day.)
(I lived well today as well.)
(Vroom, Vroom, Life on Jeju Island)
We enjoyed the video.
- Seriously. - My goodness.
- It was so nice. - Yu Ri,
it was your first time watching your daily life. How was it?
- It was my 1st time watching... - I know. It was your 1st time.
My daily activities on my day off.
"I'm on a search for my own path."
I gained more certainty for my own path.
- You said that I was doing great. - You're doing so great.
We'll root for your healthy and happy solo life!
- I had a good time. - We'll root for it.
(The much-anticipated day)
The First Rainbow Summer Retreat.
(Rainbow Club's strong team, Between Power and Ham)
(Ham!)
(Team of aces, Team Five-Way Intersection)
(Lovely 4 princesses, Pink Velvet)
(Yaho!)
(The Rainbow Club is one team.)
(A cooperative game is a must.)
(- It really feels like a retreat. - It brings back memories.)
What are you doing?
It's like a youth drama, "Our Paradise."
(The Rainbow Retreat reaches its climax.)
Please come this way.
- Yes! - Yes!
- Gosh. - Oh, my.
I haven't had this cafeteria smell...
- in a while. - I had it in high school.
- That's right. - It's so...
- It was the last time. - You haven't seen it in a while.
It's a cafeteria that brings nostalgia.
- Let's take a seat. - Let's take a seat.
- My goodness. Go on in. - It'll be tasty.
- Go on in. - Go on in.
Go on in and take a seat.
I'm so hungry after playing with water.
- It'd be a hassle to cook, - Right.
So we ordered deliveries.
- It was really neat. Seriously. - Of course.
- Cooking is exhausting. - One person needs to go...
- for the deliveries. - Okay.
- Okay. - My goodness.
CODE KUNST.
(Hungry)
There is a lot.
- Fried chicken! - Yes!
(Hurrah for fried chicken!)
- Here. - Pass it.
- Fried chicken. - What's this?
- Wait. - Be careful.
- It smells insane. - It smells good.
- There is so much food. - My goodness.
- Wait. Is it 1 chicken per person? - It's 1 chicken per person. Sit.
(Oh, yes! I can't believe it's 1 chicken per person!)
- I was so happy. - Take it out of the bag.
- Okay. - Okay.
Open it like this.
- What's with the garlic? - Gosh, it looks delicious.
- This is amazing. - There's a generous amount.
(There's a generous amount of minced garlic on top.)
Gosh, I remember that.
- Gosh, that was great. - Gosh.
(Garlic fried chicken that will blow away the heat)
The garlic won't go away even after many bites.
Right.
Why are you so angry?
I'm just so excited.
You see the garlic on top, right?
- Yes! - Yes!
You must have garlic fried chicken in the summer!
(Garlic fried chicken is the best in the summer heat.)
- Thank you! - Thank you!
The fried chicken was topped with the garlic.
- It was really good. - That was the perfect bite.
(Drooling)
This is how it should be to be called garlic fried chicken.
(Satisfied)
- Gosh, it's good. - It was really good.
- It was really good. - Right.
- There's a lot. - There has to be a lot of garlic.
- It has to be topped like this. - Right.
(Taking a big bite with a generous amount of garlic)
Gosh, it's good!
(Greatly satisfied)
There's Gye In.
- It's like watching an eating show. - She enjoyed it so much.
Right. It was a live show.
It's so good.
(Sung Hwan eats well as well.)
Gosh, that's great.
They're eating so well.
- If you're all done eating, - Right.
- Gosh. - please prepare yourselves...
for the talent show.
- Gosh. - Gosh.
- Got it? - President Jun,
are there prizes for the talent show, as well?
Of course.
Actually, today's main prizes are left for the talent show.
Hyun Moo said there's an electronic product.
There's an electronic product.
It's worth making an effort.
It's over 500 dollars.
- Really? - That's why it's important.
Isn't it an electric car?
- Yes. It's an electric car. - Her eyes are glowing.
- I was thinking of an electric car. - I think it's an electric car.
Gyeong Hye's eyes are going wild.
(Another person's eyes start glowing.)
Her eyes have become bigger.
- Right. - Gosh.
The highlight is toward the end.
This was the moment...
where we all became individuals from teammates.
- I went back in the room... - Right.
And found that everyone got rid of their wristbands.
- "We're no longer teammates." - Right.
"Forget working as a team."
Shall we move on?
- Let's go! - Right!
- You may finish up eating. - Thank you!
- That was great! - Let's go!
I think practice is over.
Let's go.
(To the long-awaited talent show venue)
Gosh, it's cool in here.
No one is here yet, right?
(Rainbow Night has begun.)
Gosh, check out the vibes.
(The moment that will bring back those exciting times)
Talent shows were the most exciting, weren't they?
- Everyone went wild for them. - I know.
I remember.
(Rainbow Night)
(The place for the Rainbow Club members' show)
(Moomoo came early to get ready.)
You were always there early to get ready.
I had to set things up.
(Feeling proud)
(Kian84 and Dae Ho arrive.)
- The 84s! - They're quick.
The 84s are quick.
You've made a lot of preparations.
Why are you wearing a gown?
I'm wearing a special outfit.
- You're hiding it. - Right.
You won't be able to imagine what is to come.
Shin Young brought a lot of things as well.
Isn't it too bright?
I like dark halls.
Hello!
(The members enter one by one.)
- They look different. - Gosh!
- That's so cute! - They look different.
That's amazing!
Are we all here? We're all here.
- We're all here! - Is everyone here?
All right. This is the highlight of the First Rainbow Summer Retreat.
The talent show will now begin!
(Full of excitement)
To get all of you motivated,
there was a bit of a strain.
The CEO of MBC sponsored the gifts.
Is that true?
- It's true. - To your right,
- there are amazing prizes... - Over there?
Hidden behind the folding screen.
- What could it be? - Awesome.
- It was amazing. - Gosh.
I tried to look from underneath, but I couldn't see anything.
Right.
The prize will now get revealed!
What could it be?
- What? - What? What is it?
(Amazed)
- What is that? - I got goosebumps.
- Gosh! - Gosh!
- I need the styler! - Gosh.
(An amazing lineup of prizes)
(Amazed)
(The prizes are welcomed with open arms.)
- Those are great prizes. - Right.
Even with just the Participation Award,
- It must be bibim ramyeon. - It must be bibim ramyeon.
You get the five-type ramyeon and instant rice set.
- Nice! - That's great.
For the Excellence Award... Do you see this?
- Red ginseng! - It's the red ginseng gift set.
- Gosh! - Red ginseng is a great prize.
For the Top Excellence Award,
you get the top-quality hotel-style bedding set.
The bedding set gets my attention.
- That's amazing. - That's a great one.
The Grand Award!
It's the styler!
(Grand Award prize, styler)
- That's amazing! - That's amazing.
I told you it was amazing.
That's amazing. I moved recently.
I really need that.
Where are you going to place that at your place?
I'm going to sleep standing.
She's going to sleep standing.
The Grand Award prize is amazing.
It's truly amazing.
(The Grand Award prize is shocking.)
Who will win it?
All right. Are you all ready?
- Yes! - Yes!
This is the highlight of the First Rainbow Summer Retreat.
This is the first performance of the talent show.
To help all of you get warmed up,
an amazing guest was invited...
- What? - in secret...
- as a guest singer. - Gosh!
- I got so excited. - The guest is in there.
- There's a guest singer! - What?
- Are you serious? - Are you serious?
Don't feel intimidated after watching the performance.
This person is a big fan of I Live Alone.
(Who is it?)
- Really? - Did they come late?
What's going on?
The guest was hiding in there.
I got so excited.
Gosh!
- What? - Come on!
(Moomoo with a taekwondo uniform)
Look at that walk.
(Even his belt has Moomoo.)
(They all get shocked.)
(Closing his eyes shut)
(Ta-da!)
It's Moo!
(Screaming)
That's an ILLIT outfit.
No way.
There's just one member.
- It's MOOILLIT. - Gosh!
MOOILLIT is here as a special guest.
Gosh, MOOILLIT!
- That's the worst! - This is "It's Moo" by MOOILLIT.
You're great at making names.
- I just need to add Moo. - Gosh.
- It's Moo! - It's Moo!
(Please just "moove" away.)
(Closing his eyes)
("It's Me," the title song of 5th-generation idol group, ILLIT)
That choreography is really hard to pull off.
It was really hard.
You need strong joints to be able to do this.
Let's head toward the styler.
I'll have one person come to the front to play the music.
- Right. - Please come up.
Press this when I tell you to.
- This? - Yes. The one in front.
Does this place have lights?
(Lighting up)
- Gosh! - Gosh!
- Aren't the lights too bright? - The lights.
- All right. - "Show! Music Core" lights.
- What's the point? - Gosh.
The lights are meaningless.
- It's so bright. - Right.
- It was so embarrassing. - It was like a public institution.
Gosh, this won't be easy to do!
We will strictly go with the incandescent lighting system.
- Okay. - It's just like a retreat.
The lights smash down against your confidence.
MOOILLIT!
- MOOILLIT! - MOOILLIT!
(Posing)
(Looking sassy)
(Perfectly synced as an ILLIT member)
Why stick him with them?
- Gosh! - I'm Wonhee.
- Here we go! - Gosh!
- All right! It's Moo! - It's Moo!
("It's Moo" by MOOILLIT)
Gosh, what is this?
(Hopping)
(My goodness!)
Look at CODE KUNST's face!
(His limbs shake about cutely.)
(Screaming)
- Go! - MOOILLIT!
(He shows off his charms with their support.)
What is that?
He's cheating.
- Go! - I forgot the moves.
What is this?
Where are you looking at? Look here!
- Jun Hyun Moo! - Go!
- Jun Hyun Moo! - He's not watching at all.
- Go! - Jun Hyun Moo!
(He has the same confidence of an ILLIT member!)
(The talented one calls for cameras.)
Gosh, thank you, Joy. She filmed it.
Let's go!
- Let's go! - It's me!
- Let's go! - Let's go!
Didn't he get an electric shock?
(Doing the choreography)
- What? - What was that?
What was that?
MOOILLIT!
Moomoo!
(Entranced with the perfect choreography)
(Moomoo!)
- Let's do it together! - MOOILLIT!
Together!
Moomoo!
(Posing)
- Gosh. - It's Moo!
- How cute! - Yes!
- The ending fairy. - Right.
(They all become fans.)
I love you!
(He belatedly feels embarrassed.)
(MOOILLIT's debut peformance was successful.)
- I'm in first place. - MOOILLIT!
I spent around 300 dollars for this.
Yesterday, in a dance studio in Apgujeong,
- Yesterday? - I did my best for three hours.
He's a fast learner.
(He was full of passion during his quick lesson.)
I didn't expect to waste 300 dollars like this.
- The performance ended so quickly. - You spent a lot on this.
(Laughing)
After the guest singer's performance,
who will go next?
(Who will go next?)
Is it better to get it over with first?
Everyone looked hesitant to go first.
(Hesitating)
It made me feel nervous.
What do we do?
Let's stay low for now.
(Avoiding the next turn with all of their might)
- We're ready. - Should we go?
- What do you think, Sung Hwan? - Is it better...
to get it over with first?
I'm fine. Should we go?
- Really? - Yes.
- Let's do it. - Park Gyeong Hye?
- Will you go next? - I'll get it over with first.
Park Gyeong Hye!
- Let's go! - And Ku Sung Hwan!
- These two are together? - Nice!
It's Ku Sung Hwan and Park Gyeong Hye!
(They shyly make their appearance with the cheers.)
- What? - Gosh!
- You look amazing! - Gosh!
- You look amazing! - He has a mic.
- He has a mic. - You have a grain of rice here.
Right.
You have a piece of puffed grain!
The garlic.
The garlic fried chicken!
(It must be the garlic fried chicken.)
That's the fun of it.
- That's the fun of a retreat. - That's the fun of it.
- Hello. - Hello.
- This is... - This is...
- the Glutton! - the Goblin!
(Screaming)
That sounds so old-fashioned. The Glutton and the Goblin.
The Glutton and the Goblin.
If you two are ready, I will play the song.
(Feeling anxious)
Can I go out for a while?
- Can I go out for a while? - No!
I watched my performance, Gyeong Hye.
I watched my own performance.
I'll muster up my courage to watch this.
(Opening her eyes wide)
(Rainbow Night)
(The familiar intro strikes the heart.)
- It's this one! - This is it.
- "Candy in My Ear!" - Gosh!
- "Candy in My Ear!" - Yes!
("Candy in My Ear" by Glutton and Goblin)
Let's go!
- Goblin! - Goblin!
(Screaming)
Park Gyeong Hye!
(Jumping up and down out of embarrassment)
(What am I doing?)
- Nice one! - I love you!
(Baek Gyeong Hye reveals her sweet voice.)
- Goblin! - Goblin!
(It has to be what you want to hear)
(Singing like a tiger)
- Gosh, it's Ok Taec Yeon. - What's this?
- Ku Taec Yeon. - Ku Taec Yeon.
(Swinging)
(He sends a mysterious sign.)
I got goosebumps.
(Screaming)
(I love you)
(Approaching)
It's the same performance, right?
(Is it hard to distinguish?)
(It's so sweet)
(It doesn't feel like words)
(Perfect choreography)
Check out his outfit!
(Equipped with abs)
What are you doing, Sung Hwan?
What is he wearing inside?
- I love you! - Goblin!
- What's with the abs? - Goblin!
Goblin!
(The song reaches the climax.)
What? What was that?
(Real candy appears.)
Yes!
What? What was that?
(Rushing over)
What was that?
(They all go wild over the sweet performance.)
This was a real dog fight.
I love you!
(Moomoo rushes over.)
(What about me?)
Candy!
(Eating)
- That's awful. - That was cute.
Thank you so much.
(Thank you for enjoying the candy.)
- Candy! - Candy!
(She sings her heart out in the mess.)
(The audience goes wild with the sugar high.)
The candy made me go hyper.
This is hilarious.
That was great!
(Ku Taec Yeon tore it up!)
(Appalled)
- What was that? - Brother!
- What was that? - It will be hard to believe,
but we practiced five times before this.
- Five times? - Yes.
(Starting with individual practices, )
(the two worked hard together.)
He was serious about this performance.
He called me a week before the performance...
and asked if I had a suit with printed muscles.
- It would've felt empty without it, - Right.
- so he asked for a suit. - A proper outfit.
- He was serious about it. - He was serious about it.
(Ku Taec Yeon and Baek Gyeong Hye were serious.)
Nice one!
After feeling pumped up by this performance,
the next performer should step forward.
Carry on with this energy.
- Carry on with this energy. - Feel the energy.
Go first.
(Avoiding eye contact)
Gosh, that was amazing.
- Let's go. - Anyone?
I'll go next!
- All right. - The amazing singer.
(A round of applause for Na Ra for stepping up)
Hello.
Please bring up the volume. The reverb.
- Right. - "The reverb."
I was told that nothing was changed.
I'm an actor in I Live Alone.
My name is Bae Na Ra. It's a pleasure to meet you.
- Right. - Yes!
- An actor in I Live Alone? - Right.
- Being here... - Let's go!
In this retreat...
reminded me of my retreats as a student.
That was why I prepared this song.
I continued to dream...
while singing this song.
Please follow along if you know this one.
- Sounds great. - Okay!
Here's the song.
I think Na Ra will sing a ballad.
I thought for a month...
before picking this song.
(The reliable musical actor with 14 years of experience)
Gosh, he looks great.
Bae Na Ra!
(A relieving singing voice trained by musicals)
You look different.
I really wanted to...
- watch his musicals. - Right.
I felt so grateful to be able to watch you sing in person.
Really? Thank you so much!
Please come to my musical.
- I would love to! - Right!
(Which song did the seasoned singer pick after a month?)
(Guitar strumming)
Gosh!
("Thorn" by Buzz)
(The song everyone knows just by hearing the intro!)
(Rainbow Night)
- The song of memories. - It was over from that moment!
(Strumming)
("Thorn" by Bae Na Ra)
Buzz!
One, two, three.
"One, two, three."
Bae Na Ra with milky skin!
(The verse sounds sweet.)
(Impressed)
(Amazed)
(A voice that brings back memories)
He has a great tone.
I love you!
(Na Ra gets immersed into the song as well.)
(Ku Taec Yeon gets lost in his memories.)
Gosh! It's Ku Taec Yeon.
(Hissing)
(To stop time from taking you away)
You must sing along to this one.
Everyone knows this song.
He's a great singer.
The vein popping out on his neck looks impressive.
It really feels like a retreat.
(Na Ra's song brings back retreat vibes.)
- Let's go! - Let's go!
(Your memory)
(Past love)
(Immersed)
(He shares those memories with the audience.)
That made it really feel like a retreat.
- Right. - That made it feel like a retreat.
(Grabbing)
(She sings her heart out after snatching the mic.)
(Singing with her head voice)
(This song must be sung with the head.)
This has to be done.
You must use the head voice.
(The song reaches the climax.)
- You! - Bae Na Ra!
Look at Bum June.
(I felt so afraid)
- Bae Na Ra! - Bae Na Ra!
(I missed you)
(Like crazy)
(Now)
(Let go of me)
He's an amazing singer.
- Nice! - Don't cry!
- You sang your heart out! - Don't cry!
Gosh! That was Musical Actor...
- Bae Na Ra! - Why is he tearing up?
- I love you! - Gosh!
(Full of lingering feelings)
Buzz...
was the karaoke president for men.
Gosh. Buzz's songs...
filled up the charts with...
- songs like "A Vacation to Me." - That's right.
- "Coward." - "Coward" was a must.
All right.
- Let's wait one more turn. - One more turn?
- I need some time. - What?
- I feel so nervous right now. - This feels like the right time.
- This feels like the right time. - I feel so nervous right now.
It should come after a ballad song.
All right.
Don't waste any more time.
(Peeking)
- Who will go next? - Don't waste any more time.
The most-awaited...
group will go next. The 84s!
(The 84s will go next.)
(I can't watch this.)
I'm excited!
- Let's go! - Let's go!
What did they prepare? I'm curious.
(Peeking)
These two must really want the prize.
It's amazing.
Kian84 is going this far?
There's a reason why they needed some time.
There's a big transformation.
- A transformation? - Right.
- They're dressing up. - I feel nervous.
Are we going too far?
- No. - This should be fine, right?
What's the point of talking about this right now?
Right.
Come on!
Gosh. Let's just do it.
They talked with each other a lot in there.
- I heard them talk. - Right.
Right.
They're really regretting it.
They practiced so hard...
- in the hallway. - Right.
Please come out when you're ready.
- Oh, my gosh! - Gosh!
Oh, my gosh!
(The Grand Award is ours! It's the 84s!)
- The 84s! - Seo Taiji!
Please come out when you're ready.
- Oh, my gosh! - Gosh!
Oh, my gosh!
(They've transformed into Seo Taiji and Boys.)
- The 84s! - It's Seo Taiji!
- Their hats are so cute. - I used to be cool.
I want that beanie.
- Really? - It's so cute.
How did you engrave 84 on the hat?
I cut the packing tape and stuck on it.
The 84s!
Please say hello.
All right. We are Seo Taiji and Lee Juno.
It's good to see you, Taiji and Juno.
(Your junior, Ku Taec Yeon, would like to say hello.)
They must love Seo Taiji and Boys.
Gosh, they look the same.
Let's find out which song of Seo Taiji and Boys they chose.
We'll play the song now.
(Fully expectant)
(Wait, this song is...)
This is crazy.
- What is this? - I must watch this standing up.
I must watch this standing up.
You're performing to this song?
("Come Back Home" by Taiji84 and Juno84)
I can't watch this.
Taiji84 and Juno84
(Are you ready, buddy?)
(Of course.)
(For the synced dancing they admired when they were young)
- They did practice! - We practiced a lot!
- You practiced hard. - After all that practice?
Dae Ho used to dance.
Yes, Dae Ho was in a dance club.
- Really? - Yes.
Oh, my.
(Back to when we were 12)
Gosh, Kim Dae Ho!
(Cheering)
Let's go!
(Chuckling)
This is driving me crazy.
Let's go!
(The 84s's teamwork is as good as the original singers.)
Goodness.
Let's go!
(I've seen the end of my life)
(My heart felt frustrated)
(It calls for a group singing.)
(Taiji84's fast-paced voice)
(Juno84's turn)
(After seeing my abandoned self)
(My abandoned self)
(I didn't exist)
(An announcer's articulate rap)
(Falling for the charm of two men who have opposite charms)
(Finally)
(The original dance)
That was the highlight move.
(Flailing around)
(Peeking)
(My parents' suppression started again)
I think he wrote the lyrics on his palm.
He couldn't memorize that part.
Lift your heads!
(Our heads?)
(Halting)
(Quickly singing the song)
Was he actually in a dance club?
(It's okay because we're still young)
(Feeling bad)
(Tearful display of fighting spirit by the youngsters born in 1984)
(Come back home)
In the place to be
- There's something more. - What is it?
Let's go!
In the place to be
- There's something more. - What is it?
(Dance time)
Let's go!
(One, two, three, four)
Hold on.
What is this?
(What is that?)
(The dance break is rather dirty.)
(They keep going.)
You should go lower.
(Just keep going!)
In the place to be
What is this?
(Flapping)
The geese.
- Where are you going? - They're running away!
- Where are you going? - Wrap it up before you go!
They flew away.
(Moved)
Gosh, that was amazing.
What a unique ending.
Kian84's tone was similar to Taiji's tone.
Seriously, Kian84's rap was so good.
It was Taiji's tone.
(I've seen the end of my life)
(My heart felt frustrated)
(Taiji84 brought out Seo Taiji's features well.)
(Meanwhile, Taiji84)
Our performance ended just like that.
Doesn't the atmosphere seem a bit off?
- I'm not sure. - Right?
They're upset that it didn't turn out as well as they practiced.
(Upset that their performance was shaky)
We shouldn't have done it.
Kian84 also wrote something on his palm.
- Good job, though. - Good job.
All right. Next...
- Darn it. - Gosh, it's hot.
(You did so well.)
Well done!
Well done.
Someone who gained courage by their performance...
can go next.
- I'll go. - Okay.
- Here he goes! - Lee Seon Min!
Oh, my gosh!
Okay!
Let's go, SBS's official recruit comedian!
- Yes, let's go! - Lee Seon Min!
- Hey! - Lee Seon Min!
Seon Min is a pro, so he wouldn't ruin it, would he?
Unlike us.
What could it be?
- What could it be? - I'm curious.
I was surprised by him backstage.
No one can keep up with comedians' ideas.
Something you've never imagined is happening now.
- I'm curious. - It's the best.
I can't wait to see it.
Can you lay out a mat?
You want me to lay out a mat?
(Heave-ho)
- I just need to lay it out? - Yes.
Fold it and put another one on top.
(A huge mat appears out of the blue.)
What is it?
(What is that?)
Seeing mats like that made us more expectant.
- That's right. - I'm so curious.
What could it be? Four mats?
It's a comedy you should pay to watch.
That's right.
It's the kind of comedy you should buy a ticket for.
I can't wait to see it.
Everyone, here comes Lee Seon Min!
(Seon Min is ready.)
It was the highlight of the day.
It was the best one for me.
Seriously. You're right.
It deserved the Grand Award.
The highlight of the day.
- You've got a friend in me - What is this?
(The person who appeared for the Rainbow Club's night)
You've got a friend in me
(Buzz Lightyear)
What is this?
I thought it was Trainer Yang Chi Seung.
Trainer Yang Chi Seung?
(He's quite big to be called Buzz Lightyear.)
(A solid build)
To infinity and beyond.
To infinity and beyond!
Andy is here!
(Andy?)
(Falling)
What was that?
(So...)
(what are you going to do now?)
(I can't take it anymore.)
(Biggest humiliation since his debut)
No, you must watch it!
No! Watch it!
- I can't watch it! Yaho! - You must watch it!
- Hey, watch! - I'm too embarrassed to watch!
Open your eyes!
- Open your eyes! Watch! - He can't watch it!
- Time will pass if you just watch. - Okay.
He's sweating so much.
(Sweating like crazy)
(Meanwhile, the audience members are sweating here.)
You must watch it.
- Andy left! - Andy left!
(Getting up)
To infinity and beyond.
- To infinity... - Andy is here!
- Andy is here! - Andy is here!
(Rolling)
- Only the two of them like it. - I didn't understand.
The mood is turning awkward, right?
"The mood is turning awkward, right?"
What? They are...
We were so consoled by Seon Min's performance.
- Andy left! - Andy left!
(The more Andy comes and goes...)
Andy is here!
- Andy is here! - He keeps doing that.
- Andy left! - Andy left!
You asked me to lay out the mat for this?
- What is that? - Andy is here!
(Feeling refreshed)
- Andy left. - He left.
Andy left.
(Goodbye)
He did well.
My top pick.
Thank you.
Seriously.
- Lee Seon Min! - Lee Seon Min!
- Lee Seon Min! - Are you okay?
- Lee Seon Min! - Hold on.
- To do this... - To do this...
You asked me to lay out a mat?
- Look. He laughed the loudest. - I laughed the loudest.
(Laughing)
That's all?
This is it.
All right.
- You see? - Nice.
- Kian84. I mean... - Gosh, this team...
I practiced tumbling on a mat for 30 minutes.
Really? What did you do?
(He put on a swim cap with determination.)
(He threw himself for 30 minutes.)
For 30 minutes?
I had to train myself.
You did a breakfall...
- more than a judo player would. - That's right.
Give him applause!
(Please give an applause to my junior nonetheless!)
Thank you!
Seon Min is running away too.
- I feel so relieved. - I'm so thankful to Seon Min.
I feel so much better now.
They all look so serious.
All right. The next performance...
(The next performance that will continue this odd atmosphere.)
is by MINHO!
Gosh, MINHO was crazy good.
MINHO gained confidence.
- Let's go, MINHO! - He didn't seem nervous at all...
- when he went in to prepare. - That's right.
It's something that only MINHO could do.
- That's right. - Right.
The 2nd week of July, 2026.
The ace of his team,
MINHO will sing it!
- "As I Told You!" - He's just...
("As I Told You" originally sung by Kim Sung Jae)
MINHO will sing it! "As I Told You!"
(Everyone gets up.)
This is crazy!
(Using the incandescent light bulbs Instead of fancy lighting today)
Please give him a big round of applause.
It was over then.
(Full of passion from the start)
(Let's go, MINHO!)
It reminded me of the old days so much.
- He's good. - He's so cool.
- There's nothing he can't do. - Seriously.
- MINHO! - MINHO!
- I love you, MINHO! - MINHO!
(Coming down the stage while he's at it)
We love you!
(Dancing)
I loved it.
(This is nice!)
(They're dancing together in no time.)
(Continuing the momentum)
(Let's go!)
(Dancing naturally)
(Going back to the past while singing and dancing)
(He brought them back to 30 years ago.)
(MINHO's passionate stage)
- We love you, MINHO! - Come on!
(This is what you call a talent show.)
He's indeed an idol.
I was sad that it was too short.
(MINHO is the best.)
- He's so cool. - Applause!
It was a 100-percent sync.
(Feeling proud)
This was so cool.
He had the same outfit too.
How do you do it?
(Gosh, that was so cool.)
It's about time we see her performance.
Everyone's performance, including mine,
was just a teaser for her performance.
I saw her getting ready. It's incredible.
- You saw it? - You'll see when you see her.
(The highly expected next performance)
Hello, everyone. Nice to meet you!
(Screaming)
You were serious about it!
I cheered really loudly. I loved it.
- It's great to see you! - Aunt Da Mi!
- Hello, everyone. Nice to meet you! - It's Da Vi.
(Aunt Da Vi)
("Within 10 Minutes" by Aunt Da Vi)
- Aunt Da Vi! - Aunt Da Vi!
(Yes, I'll trust you)
(Pulling)
The wandering mic. It never comes near your mouth.
(Dancing)
- He loves it. - Ji Hyeon loves it.
Ji Hyeon loves it.
(With passionate energy from Aunt Da Vi, )
(everyone is dancing along.)
(She even wipes her mic with her armpit.)
Ji Hyeon seriously loves it.
(Head, throat, chest, stomach)
I sang with all my body.
(Within 10 minutes)
- Aunt Da Vi! - Aunt Da Vi!
(Ending her performance with a heart)
- You're the best. Thank you. - Thank you.
- She's the best. - Stay healthy.
Yes, thank you.
- Yes. - Aunt, stay healthy!
- She's the best. - She's amazing.
I can't believe I got to see her.
- CODE KUNST, are you ready? - CODE KUNST!
- Let's go! - CODE KUNST!
I couldn't wait to see his performance.
I can't wait to see his performance.
I know.
(He appears while pushing a table.)
- Magic? - Will he show a magic trick?
(Is it perhaps a magic trick?)
- It's not a magic trick. - It's not a magic trick.
It'd be amazing if he did DJ'ing.
- That'd be amazing. - Everyone.
Could it be cup stacking?
- Speed cup stacking. - I see.
He's like Lee Eun Gyeol.
He looks sexy.
(Jealous)
(CODE KUNST's talent show)
It's a tablecloth-pulling trick.
(A tablecloth-pulling trick)
It's a tablecloth-pulling trick...
that even Choi Hyun Woo and Lee Eun Gyeol can't do.
Okay.
- He can't do it? - Choi Hyun Woo can't do it.
- He can't? - No.
I mean...
- Let's see. - Let's go.
- That's a bit... - Shouldn't you pull it a little?
Cover it properly.
- He didn't cover it fully. - It looks hard.
- I know. - Please...
cover the table fully.
- The tablecloth... - You'll see...
that all experts don't do it like that.
(Laying the tablecloth like an expert)
- No way. - This is hard.
- This is hard. - This is really hard to do.
There are so many things.
You're going this far?
This is hard to do.
This... Hey, that's too many.
Wouldn't that be hard?
- Seriously? - You're stacking up that many?
- I feel it'll be three floors. - Yes.
- I'll approve of that. - It'll be amazing if he does it.
- I'd approve of it. - I would too.
- Today... Gosh. - I'd approve of that.
(Shall I begin?)
Gosh, he's charismatic.
(Watch carefully.)
(The expert grabbed the tablecloth.)
Gosh, it's so embarrassing.
(Gosh, it's so embarrassing.)
- Lift your head. - No! Lift your head.
- Why? - No. Lift your head.
- You should watch it too. - You were serious. Watch.
- Watch. - You should watch it too.
You were serious. Watch.
Don't close your eyes and watch it closely!
You must watch it.
Open your eyes wide and watch.
- You must watch it. - Even Seon Min held it in.
Of course. You must watch it.
You must watch.
(The expert gets started.)
- Go. - Let's go.
If he succeeds in it, he should take the styler.
Why is the background song so sexy?
It's my song.
(It's time to show off the expert's skills.)
(Laughing)
(Embarrassed)
It's hard to make so many fall.
- What is this? - What is this?
(The expert's tower fell.)
(Chuckling)
- There's Level Four. - Okay.
- Do Level 4. - Level 4.
Will you break more glasses for Level Four?
He's my close friend, and I'm so embarrassed.
He wasn't like that before.
(He brought in the props for Level 4.)
These are block toys.
I assembled them myself.
What? Wait.
That's expensive.
- Gosh. - He assembled these himself,
but if they end up like this, they'll all break.
They'll all be broken.
- If they break, that's the end. - That's right.
I'll approve of it if you put these...
on top of the wine glasses.
- I'll have to add some water. - Go ahead and add water.
They're too light, so please add some water.
- This is the real deal. - Goodness.
Yes, he needs to lay them out first.
(Thinking)
Even with water...
It'll be doable because it'll be heavier.
If you succeed, you'll be a step closer to the styler.
Okay.
Will that be possible?
- I don't think so. - Will this be possible?
If he succeeds, then he gets the styler for sure.
- It'd be a Guinness World Record. - Seriously.
Yes, he'll win the styler for sure if he does it.
If you don't want to do it, you can say it now.
I'll do it.
- He's so cool. - He even prayed.
He's so determined.
(You can do it.)
- Let's go! - Let's do it.
This was nerve-racking.
Right, it was so...
(The expert goes for Level 4.)
Let's go!
Please!
Gosh!
Please, CODE KUNST!
- Please! - Let's go!
(Pulling)
(Grabbing)
(No, my block toys!)
(They were relieved too.)
You made it!
(Did you see my success?)
You did it.
- Why did he do that? - Why did he gesture that?
To call me if there's a gig.
I see.
- Hey. - What was that for?
(I'll call you.)
- Hold on. That's... - Hold on.
The last bit was weird.
You looked too pathetic toward the end.
- No. - He looked really pathetic.
When you did this at the end.
(The last movement was a bit iffy.)
I was afraid it'd fly off since it's a plane.
- It was about to take off. - It was about to launch.
Look at his reflexes.
To save his block toys.
What is that?
(I saved my block toys.)
- The two were saved! - Only the two survived.
He saved his toys.
Give him applause.
He did it.
(Congratulations.)
He saved his block toys only.
An amazing performance awaits us.
- Seriously. - Here comes the main performance.
The final grand show.
Let's watch Cool's performance.
They're the youngest.
Joy gathered the other two...
to perform together.
- Yes. - The youngest ones.
Two, three.
- Cooling Cooling. - Cooling Cooling.
Hello, we're the youngest of the show.
- Ji. - Jo.
And Bum.
- Jijobum. - Yes!
Joy.
- Joy. - Buzz is excited.
No one is watching you,
so why were you doing that?
It was my last shred of pride.
This is amazing.
A performance by Cooling Cooling that dominated this summer.
(Expectant)
Here we go.
Ji!
Jo!
Bum!
He's excited.
(The atmosphere is heated.)
I love "Sorrow."
Don't they look like vitamins? With their outfits too.
(Refreshing)
It looks like a music show.
(This looks like...)
(200 percent in sync with Cool)
Let's go!
(A perfect recreation of that era)
He looks the same.
He sounds really similar to Lee Jae Hoon.
Right. He wasn't only good at trot songs.
(Old memories come flooding back.)
- What are you doing? - What are you doing?
(That's not it)
(A voice as clear as tinkling jade beads)
She's good.
(A perfect match for a refreshing 90s-style vocal)
They sound the same.
(Their mouths are drying from too much smiling.)
Look at Buzz.
(Staring intently)
Did you lose circulation?
Why are you doing that?
He wanted to showcase Buzz as much as possible.
- No matter what... - He...
He wasn't that interested in the performance.
He just had to show his talent.
(Taking his chance)
The cap must've been really tight.
So it was tight, just like Joy's name.
- It was tight. - And Joy was there.
(I'm the real deal.)
(Go away.)
They're good.
(Even their performance was perfect.)
(Hitting the high notes refreshingly)
- He's so good. - Who knew it could be so easy?
I know.
To make this performance...
- You recorded it too? - That's crazy.
(The youngest members blew the stage away.)
(Dance perfectly in sync)
(Refreshing)
(Take a chance and trust me this once)
I wish I could project my voice like that.
(Setting off with the rap he rewrote)
Let's go!
(Among the many people who saw that)
(Many of them are my friends)
(No way, I can't believe it)
Let's go, I Live Alone
(Cooling Cooling is indeed great.)
- Cooling Cooling. - Cooling Cooling.
- Cooling Cooling. - I loved it.
That was amazing.
That was great. You're amazing.
(I approve of it.)
- I'm sorry. - A scene stealer.
- What is that? - I was so impressed.
The cap was too tight...
that it looks like his eyes are bulging.
(This was Cooling Cooling.)
I want to see them perform again.
- They did well. - I liked the song they chose.
They did really well.
I think they are a strong favorite to win.
They're almost like the Grand Award winner.
We'll wrap this up...
- after voting. - Oh, we're voting?
Please take ballots.
Write down the team whom you think did the best.
You are voting for two teams, excluding yourself.
(They can only vote for 2 teams.)
Who should I vote?
Everyone worked so hard to prepare this.
I know. Everyone was more serious about this than I thought.
(It was too intense that it's not easy to vote.)
Two teams, excluding yourself.
(They finished voting in secret.)
Are you all done?
(A wide variety of generous prizes)
(Time to determine the final winner)
Lee Seon Min will help us count the votes.
- I'll write it down. - Gosh, Buzz.
Buzz helped us count the votes.
(Nervous)
Glutton and Goblin.
(The first team to win a vote is Glutton and Goblin.)
Thank you!
MINHO!
(MINHO wins a vote.)
MINHO was excited.
(Keeping the record on the white board)
Aunt Da Vi!
Cooling Cooling!
(Aunt Da Vi, Cooling Cooling)
Lee Seon Min!
(Aunt Da Vi, Cooling Cooling, Seon Min)
Bae Na Ra!
(Aunt Da Vi, Cooling Cooling, Seon Min, Na Ra)
- Buzz! - Gosh, seriously.
- MOOILLIT! - Gosh, MOOILLIT.
MOOILLIT.
- We weren't to write our own names! - I'm sure you wrote your name.
We'll get one vote, at least.
(Everyone is getting a vote.)
Cooling Cooling!
(Only the 84s and CODE KUNST haven't received a vote.)
Aunt Da Vi!
Glutton and Goblin!
(MINHO, Cooling Cooling, Seon Min, Na Ra, Glutton and Goblin...)
- MINHO! - Gosh!
Darn it.
Just one vote...
Please give us one vote.
Cooling Cooing!
(Cooling Cooling is getting ahead with the momentum.)
(Cooling Cooling)
You're not supposed to be happy now.
(Lowering his head)
We weren't getting any votes,
and Dae Ho kept going, "Cooling Cooling."
(It's not time to rejoice when I don't have a vote yet.)
All right.
Cooling Cooling!
This is amazing.
They were leading by a huge margin.
We might win first place.
Kim Shin Young!
(Aunt Da Vi: 4)
Joy, Park Ji Hyeon, Seo Bum June!
(Cooling Cooling: 5)
Aunt Da Vi!
- It's 5 to 5. - It's a tie!
It's neck to neck.
Aunt Da Vi!
(Aunt Da Vi: 6, Cooling Cooling: 5)
Cooling Cooling!
(Aunt Da Vi: 6, Cooling Cooling: 6)
It's a close match.
Aunt Da Vi!
(Aunt Da Vi: 7, Cooling Cooling: 6)
Gosh, only CODE KUNST and we didn't get any votes.
It's the last one.
Aunt Da Vi and Cooling Cooling are neck and neck.
(They're neck and neck with a vote difference.)
We don't know yet.
First place.
(Who will take the last vote?)
It's only a vote difference.
(Nervous)
(A fancy performance and stage presence)
(Aunt Da Vi)
(They instantly brought back the old days.)
It really looks like "Show! Music Core."
(Cooling Cooling)
(Will it be a decisive win...)
(or a draw?)
Aunt Da Vi!
(Aunt Da Vi)
- I was really surprised. - Aunt Da Vi...
wins!
She beat Cooling Cooling with two votes.
Aunt Da Vi takes the win.
Congratulations!
You're awesome!
(The Grand Award prize goes to Shin Young.)
Up next...
The Top Excellence Award goes to Cooling Cooling.
Cooling Cooling.
I'm really happy that we won the Top Excellence Award.
I'd like to dedicate this honor to you.
(I'd like to dedicate this honor to the Rainbow Club members.)
The Excellence Award. Congratulations.
(Glutton and Goblin, MINHO, and Seon Min take the Excellence Award.)
Next is the Encouragement Award.
- It's me! - MOOILLIT!
- MOOILLIT! - MOOILLIT!
- It was me. - You won.
I got two votes.
Let's go!
Everyone, thank you!
Congratulations!
- Great work. - Great job.
- Great job. - Great job.
- Great job, Hyun Moo. - Well done.
Hey.
- They're all different? - Take them.
Hyun Moo shared them with us.
Yes, the spicy noodles.
Na Ra, this...
- After it ended. - No.
(Na Ra, take this.)
After a get-together, we become really close.
I was really happy with the retreat itself.
(Rainbow Night)
(A Good Day Spent Together, the end)
(Next story)
(Ju Seung is heading somewhere with his mom?)
(Packed with things)
(Grandma!)
(This is Ju Seung's Grandma's place.)
(For Grandma who is feeling lonely after Grandpa left)
(Good grandson Ju Seung has come!)
(Massaging with his hands)
(He does his best to take care of her health.)
(So she doesn't get depressed, )
(he also feeds her something delicious.)
(Smiling broadly thanks to the good grandson)
(I'm happy too if you smile, Grandma.)
(And the biggest gift for his grandma)
(A winning trophy from a director survival show)
I won first place.
(He became a director...)
(just as his grandfather wanted.)
(I donated all 100,000 dollars...)
(that I won as a prize, just as Grandpa wanted.)
(Thank you...)
Your grandpa...
- I know. He would've loved it. - would've loved it.
Yes.
(A Rewarding Day to Give Back to My Grandparents)
(Real...)
(Running)
(They gathered because...)
(they wanted to run.)
Stick it well so it doesn't fall off.
(Three men)
(Kian84)
(MINHO)
(Na Ra)
(Let's go!)
(We...)
(run in the mountains.)
(Uphill...)
(and downhill)
(It's much more fun if we run together.)
(Happy)
This is fun.
(It was fun because we cheered each other up.)
- One, two, three. - Two, three.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
- Okay. Let's show them who we are. - Shall we?
(Ready, Set, Go)